Mss.B.In6
American Philosophical Society
William T. (William Thornton) Innes papers, ca. 1898-1969
Circa 1898-1969
Mss.B.In6
American Philosophical Society
2.5 Linear feet Ca. 2500 items
There are letters, sketches of fish, and other documents that pertain to Innes' interest in exotic fishes for home aquariums and their care. There is information on the journal Aquarium which he founded in 1932, and minute books of the Aquarium Society of Philadelphia, 1898-1912 (3 vol.). The most voluminous professional correspondence is with George S. Myers, and there is some family correspondence.
Ca. 2500 items.
Innes, William T., (William Thornton), 1874-1969
Box 1-4
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Gift from the William T. Innes estate and accessioned, 4/--/1969 (1970 126ms).
Biographical/Historical note
William Thornton Innes was a Philadelphia publisher and editor.
Aquarium Society of Philadelphia.; Myers, George S., (George Sprague), 1905-1985; Aquarium fishes.; Aquariums.; Fish-culture.; Minutes.; Sketches.
- Series I. Correspondence
  - Ade, George, 1936 March; 2.0 items (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alessandroni, Eugene V. to William Innes, 1929 May 7; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Alessandroni, Eugene V. to William T. Innes
    Discussion of work being done at the McCall School.
  - American Automobile Association, 1952 April 15; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 3)
    American Automobile Association
    A letter seeking the advice of William Innes in regards to identifying the sex of several fish.
  - American Book Company, 1934 November 10; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 4)
    American Book Company
    A letter to William Innes explaining the system of marking in the "Manual of Botany."
  - American Institute of Graphic Arts, 1924 May 7; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 5)
    American Institute of Graphic Arts
    An invitation to the "Annual Meeting of the American Institute of Graphic Arts."
  - American Society of Ichthyologists and Herpetologists, 1931 August 12; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 6)
    American Society of Ichthyologists and Herpetologists
    A letter addressed to William Innes. The letter identifies and describes several fish recently photographed by Innes.
  - Andrew, Elizabeth to William Innes, 1944, 1946; 2.0 items (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Aquarist and Pondkeeper, 1948; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Aquarium Society of Philadelphia, 1908-1917; 7.0 items (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Arnold, Johann Paul, 1947-1948; 11.0 items (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Axelrod, Herbert R., 1954-1966; 31.0 items (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Bailey, J. It., 1952; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Baker, Blue, 1946; 3.0 items (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Ballentine, Fred M., 1966; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Ballentine, Margaret, 1965; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Barnes, Maurice, 1948; 2.0 item (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Barrett, Franklin., undated; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Baylor, C. C., 1948; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Bedford, Duke of, undated; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Belcher, Wilda, 1948; 3.0 items (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Beldt, Otto, 1929-1967; 12.0 items (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Belsterling, Jean Lines, 1963-1965; 4.0 items (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Bobman, Harry B., 1935; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Bory Latour-Marliac, Joseph, undated; 2.0 items (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Boston Acquarium Society, Inc., 1959; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Breitenfeld, Frederick, 1939; 3.0 items (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Breder, C. M., Jr., 1935-1939; 2.0 items (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Brittan, Martin R., 1955; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Caidwell, Sam Y., 1946; 3.0 items (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Chapman, E. M., undated; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Chessex, Charles, 1935; 2.0 items (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - ChiavarI, G. G., 1941; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Chute, Walter H., 1934; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Clarke, Jacob One, 1928; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Close, Lyman V., 1935; 3.0 items (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Coates, C. VI, 1955; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Coker, R. E., 1935; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Colorado Aquarium Society, 1951; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Combes, Mrs. Eleanor, 1966; 2.0 items (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Conant, Roger, 1965; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Crescent Fish Farm, 1933-1948; 3.0 items (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Cronin, David Edward, 1910; 2.0 items (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Cura, L., and Sons, 1953; 2.0 items (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Curtis, Cyrus H. K., 1930; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Dearden, Robert R., Jr., 1936; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Deville, William, 1953; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - De Voe, Charles, 1941; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Dill, Harold VI, 1954; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Ditmers, Raymond L., 1919; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Dittrich, Frank E., 1954; 2.0 items (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Dorsey, Lewis M., 1934; 2.0 items (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Doscher, John VI, 1962; 2.0 items (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Dos Passos, Cyril F., 1932; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Dreer, Henry A., 1921; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Drummond, Mrs. J. E., 1966; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Dungan, Alice M., 1935; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Durau, Carl, 1946-1948; 6.0 items (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Eastman, Oliver R, 1936; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Elliott, Barbara, 1947; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Embody, George C., 1935; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Encyclopaedia Britannica, 1935; 2.0 items (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Enterprise Aquatic Society, 1954; 3.0 items (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Eugenidis, A., 1936; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Fasciano, Meade, 1966; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Fassett, N. C., 1946; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Ferguson, Herbert S., 1967; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Ferguson, William C., Jr., 1933; 3.0 items (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Finkenbine, Chris, 1952; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Finley, Mrs. H. VI, 1930; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Flesch, Mrs. A., 1946; 2.0 items (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Fletcher, Alan N., 1952; 10.0 items (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Fogg, John N. Jr., 1935; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Ford, Russell, 1932; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Formont, Charles L., 1955; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Fowler, Henry VI, 1954; 2.0 items (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - French Press and Information Service, 1946; 2.0 items (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Frey, Hans, 1950; 2.0 items (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Friese, Uwe, 1954; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Fuchs, Erich, 1949; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Gersdorff, Charles E. F., 1934; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Gilbert H., VI, 1934; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Giles, E., VI, 1934; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Gion, H. D., 1931; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Godwin, S., 1955; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Gordon, Myron, 1930-1951; 10.0 items (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Graphic Arts, 1923-1926; 3.0 items (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Gray, Roger, 1935; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Green, Harold T., 1929; 2.0 items (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Greenberg, Albert, 1946; 2.0 items (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Gudger, B., VI, 1935; 2.0 items (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Guppy material, 1952; 14.0 items (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Haley, Mrs. Ann, 1957; 7.0 items (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Hart, Mrs. Florence B., 1944; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Hartel, Hernann, 1949; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Hayer, Fritz, 1930; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Heinken, Hermann and Gerhard, 1935; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Heitzman, John Richard, 1955; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Hems, Jack, 1936; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Herre, Albert W., 1937; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Heusden, A. E. van, 1948; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Hewes, J. C., undated; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Hill, Melvin H., 1935; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Hoffman, Bob, 1935; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Homer, Mrs. Virginia, undated; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Homer, William Innes, 1966; 1.0 item (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Hordes, Gertrude, 1954; 1.0 item (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Hora, Sunder Lal, 1933-1934; 4.0 items (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Horton, Alvin B., 1939; 1.0 item (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Hubbs, Carl L., 1934-1936; 4.0 items (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Iles, Gerald, 1950; 1.0 item (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Iltis, Hugo, 1951; 1.0 item (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Innes, Gray, 1966; 2.0 items (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Innes family, 1933-1965; 30.0 items (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Ives, Hubert E., 1937; 3.0 items (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Jackson, Henry E., 1939; 1.0 item (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Jackson, R. L., 1944; 3.0 items (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Jansen, D., 1933; 2.0 items (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Johaningman, Joe, Jr., undated; 1.0 item (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Johnson, Harry, 1945; 1.0 item (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Johnston, Charles E., 1943-1944; 2.0 items (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Jordan, C. Basil, 1936-1943; 13.0 items (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Jordan, David Starr, 1919; 1.0 item (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Jordan, Mrs. Elizabeth, 1966; 1.0 item (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Kempner, Stanley, 1955; 1.0 item (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Kohler, Wolfgang, 1934-1936; 4.0 items (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Kramer, Kurt, 1934; 1.0 item (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Krunpf, Ernst, 1949; 1.0 item (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Kuni, Prince, 1937; 2.0 items (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - La Gorce, John Oliver, 1919; 1.0 item (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Laughridge, Charles. The Biliteral Cipher of Francis Bacon., 1914; 1.0 item (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Laws, Mrs. Janet P., 1962-1967; 31.0 items (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Laydekev, J., 1946; 2.0 items (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Leader George N., 1965; 1.0 item (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Le Febre, S., 1948; 1.0 item (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Leith, C. W., 1935; 1.0 item (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Lingg, Joseph, 1947; 2.0 items (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Link, Henry C., 1938; 2.0 items (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Livengood, W. W., 1934; 1.0 item (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Lloyd, Rose, 1935; 1.0 item (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Lobell, Milton J., 1934; 4.0 items (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Locke, Franklin S., undated; 1.0 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Lovatt, Mrs. Mary, 1966; 1.0 item (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - McFarland, J. Horace, 1947; 1.0 item (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - McNulty, Henry S., 1952; 1.0 item (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Magee, Gray, 1944; 1.0 item (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Magee, Mrs. Elizabeth, 1957-1964; 16.0 items (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Magee, Guion and Carol, undated; 1.0 item (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Mann, W. M., 1947; 1.0 item (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Mark, E. L., 1914; 1.0 item (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Matsuno, N., 1935; 1.0 item (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Mayer, Fritz, 1929-1946; 5.0 items (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Meinken, Herman, undated; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Messner, Mrs. Ruth L., undated; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Miller, Helen S., 1946; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Miller, J. S., 1935; 2.0 items (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Ming-sin, Chan, 1945; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Montreal Aquarium Society, 1935; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Moody, Allen S., 1933; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Morris, Norman I., 1936; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Morriss, H., 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Morse, A. B, Co., 1944; 3.0 items (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Munoz, Harriet, 1966; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Myers, Frank J., 1915-1934; 6.0 items (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Myers, Frank J., Jr., 1935; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Myers, George S., No. 1, 1932-1955; 38.0 items (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Myers, George S., No. 2, 1934-1945; 10.0 items (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Myers, George S., No. 3, 1934 - 1955 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - National Aquarists Society, 1947-1948; 3.0 items (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Needham, J. G., 1920; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - New Zealand. Dominion Aquarium and Pond Society., 1948; 2.0 items (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Nichols, Henry, 1948; 9.0 items (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Noble, G. Kinglsey, 1935; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Noit, Lloyd W., 1966; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Norman, J. R., 1935; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Norwood, Robert, 1935; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - O’Malley, Henry, 1931; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Page, W. J., 1948; 2.0 items (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Pakistan Aquarium Society, 1960; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Palinkas, Ernest, 1954; 2.0 items (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Paramount Aquarium, Inc., 1942-1954; 4.0 items (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Patt, Mrs. Howard E., 1935; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Pearce, Gordon C., 1918; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Pecora Paint Co., 1918; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Perkins, Laurence E., 1949-1953; 4.0 items (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Peterkin, W. J., 1935; 2.0 items (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Peterson, Frank C., 1947; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Peterson, Theodore E., 1935; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Pilsbry, Henry A., 1936; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Pinchot, Gifford, 1922; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Pioneers of Industry Award, 1950; 2.0 items (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Pitt, W. S., 1934; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Platow and Lyon, 1933; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Powers, Ada Weigel, 1937; 2.0 items (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Price, Samuel R, 1941; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Pring, George H, 1945-1946; 23.0 items (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Prust, Erv, 1931; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Rainbow Aquarium, 1935; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Ransden, Charles T., 1936; 2.0 items (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Raughley, Morgan, 1948; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Reader, Mrs. Lee, 1932; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Reickel, Alfred O., 1952; 2.0 items (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Rivas, Luis H., 1952; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Roberts, G., 1948; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Roberts, Hervey, 1935; 6.0 items (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, 1934; 3.0 items (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Rosamond, J. A., 1951; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Rose, C., 1935-1936; 2.0 items (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Roughly, T. C., 1935; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Rowan, John, undated; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - St. Louis Globe-Democrat, 1935; 2.0 items (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - San Diego - California Club, 1946; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Sangster, Margaret E., 1931; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Sargent, William Dunlop, 1935; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Saville, Tom C., Ltd., 1954; 2.0 items (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Schaumburg, William, 1935; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Schlacks, Viola I., 1951; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Schmidt, E., 1955; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Schork, P. A., 1948; 2.0 items (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Schreitmuler, Wilhelm, 1935; 2.0 items (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Schroder, Gerhard, 1948; 2.0 items (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Schultz, Leonard P., 1953; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Scott, Creighton, 1949; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Scudder, Roger, 1954; 1.0 item (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Seale, Alvin, 1935; 1.0 item (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Shorrocks, Mrs. Eugenia S., 1935; 2.0 items (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Simkatis, Helen, 1965-1967; 8.0 items (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Slocum, Perry D., 1946; 8.0 items (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Sloet tot Everlo, A.F., and R.B. “Organization of the Netherlands Federation of Aquarium Societies.”, 1948; 2.0 items (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Smith, H. M., 1917-1933; 3.0 items (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Stalberg, Rosemary G. “Half Wits in the Woods”, etc., 1946; 7.0 items (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Stern, David, 1933; 2.0 items (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Sternke, William A., 1934-1935; 4.0 items (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Stoye, Frederick H., 1936; 4.0 items (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - “Tabloids K”, undated; 1.0 item (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Taylor, Charles M., 1946; 1.0 item (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Taylor, Walter F., 1954; 1.0 item (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Thill, Roger A., 1946; 1.0 item (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Thomas, C. C. C., 1946; 2.0 items (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Three Springs Fisheries, 1931; 2.0 items (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Thurber, Charles S., 1925; 1.0 item (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Timmerman, G. L., 1953-1956; 2.0 items (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Tomlinson, Fred J., 1945; 4.0 items (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Townsend, Charles Haskins, 1931; 1.0 item (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Traubel, Gertrude, 1946; 1.0 item (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Treuting, Herbert H., Jr., 1951; 1.0 item (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Tricker, William, 1946; 35.0 items (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Tropp, Walter William, 1954; 1.0 item (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Turner, Albert B., and Betty, 1965-1966; 8.0 items (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Typothetae Society, 1923; 1.0 item (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Ulmer, Frederick A., Jr., 1961; 1.0 item (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Vistrand, Paul, 1936; 1.0 item (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Vorderwinkler, William, 1965; 1.0 item (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Waterbury (Conn.) Aquarium Society, 1934; 1.0 item (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Weitzman, Stanley H., 1954; 1.0 item (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Welle, Monroe F., 1937; 4.0 items (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - White, Thomas D., 1941; 4.0 items (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Wilde, Oscar. Commonplace Book (from John B. Stetson. Typescript.), undated; 1.0 item (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Williams, Woodbridge, 1953; 1.0 item (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Williamson, A. A., 1946; 1.0 item (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Willinger, Allan H., 1966-1967; 6.0 items (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Wochenschrift fur Aquarien und Terroienkunde, 1935; 1.0 item (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Woodward, Carol H., 1946; 4.0 items (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Young, Barton R., 1943; 1.0 item (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Series II. Bound volumes, 9.0 items
  - "The American Characidae", 1927 May (Box 5)
    "The American Characidae"
    Volume XLIII. Part 4 of the "Memoirs of the Museum of Comparative Zoology" at Harvard College. Written by Carl H. Eigenmann.
  - "The American Characidae" No. 2, 1929 January (Box 5)
    "The American Characidae" No. 2
    Volume XLIII. Part 5 of the "Memoirs of the Museum of Comparative Zoology" at Harvard College. Written by Carl H. Eigenmann and George S. Myers.
  - "Appraisal", 1955 (Box 5)
    "Appraisal"
    A bound volume drafted by the Manufacturer's Appraisal Company. A detailed inventory of the assets of the Innes & Sons Co.
  - "Die Fremdlandischen Zierfische In Wort Und Bild", 1911; 6.0 folders (Box 5)
    "Die Fremdlandischen Zierfische In Wort Und Bild"
    A catalog of fish written by Fritz Reuter.
  - "Encyclopedia of Water Life", 1949 (Box 6)
  - "Goldfish Varieties and Tropical Aquarium Fishes: A Guide to Aquaria and Related Subjects", 1932 (Box 6)
    "Goldfish Varieties and Tropical Aquarium Fishes: A Guide to Aquaria and Related Subjects"
    The fifteenth edition of "Goldfish Varieties and Tropical Aquarium Fishes: A Guide to Aquaria and Related Subjects" written by William T. Innes.
  - "Minutes of the Aquarium Society of Philadelphia," No. 1, 1898 May 5 - 1904 December 27 (Box 6)
  - "Minutes of the Aquarium Society of Philadelphia", No. 2, 1905 January 23 - 1912 April 24 (Box 6)
  - "Minutes of the Aquarium Society of Philadelphia", No. 3, 1912 October 25 - 1914 June 24 (Box 6)
- Series III. Works by Innes, 18.0 folders (Box 7)
  - "Aquarium Fish", 1944; 1.0 item (Box 7, Folder 1)
    "Aquarium Fish"
    A copy of "Aquarium Fish: A Booklet for Beginners" written by William T. Innes.
  - "Book Reviews", 1948 November - 1949 January; 2.0 items (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - "Care of Tropical Fish", undated; 1.0 item (Box 7, Folder 3)
    "Care of Tropical Fish"
    A handwritten essay on caring for tropical fish.
  - "A Century on Chestnut Street", 1939; 1.0 item (Box 7, Folder 4)
    "A Century on Chestnut Street"
    A pamphlet written and printed by William T. Innes.
  - Financial Affairs, 1916 - 1949 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - "The First Known Blind Fish of the Family Characide: A New Genus From Mexico", 1936 December 17; 1.0 item (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - "First Principles in Aquarium Management", undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - "Greetings by Benjamin Franklin", 1939; 1.0 item (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - "Imitator Catfish", undated; 1.0 item (Box 7, Folder 9)
    "Imitator Catfish"
    A hand-written essay by William T. Innes and George S. Myers.
  - Meridian Club, undated; 1.0 item (Bin 7, Folder 10)
  - "The Modern Aquarium", 1930; 1.0 item (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper Clipping/Reviews, 1925 - 1944 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - "Notes/Miscellany", 1925 - 1935 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - "Printers' Ideas on a School for Printing", 1938 February 10; 3.0 items (Box 7, Folder 14)
    Scope and Contents note
    A copy of a manuscript titled: "Printers' Ideas on a School For Printing." Stapled to the manuscript was a letter from George A. Carter discussing the manuscript and the situation of Franklin Bache Huntington. Innes' response is posted to the back of the letter.
  - "Pronunciation of Scientific Names Used in the Following Pages", undated; 1.0 item (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - "Some Highlights in the History of Halftone", 1927 September; 1.0 item (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - "The Start: Young People's Magazine of Art, Science, and Literature", 1894 January (Box 7, Folder 17)
    "The Start: Young People's Magazine of Art, Science, and Literature"
    Includes first article written by William T. Innes.
  - "Your Aquarium", 1945 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    "Your Aquarium"
    A corrected copy, notes, handdrawn illustrations, and two finished pamphlets for "Your Aquarium" written by William T. Innes.
- Series IV. Works by Others, 24.0 folders (Box 8)
  - Beck, James M. "The Memory of Benjamin Franklin", 1924 January 18; 1.0 item (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Breder, C. M., Jr., "Zoologica", 1934 June; 1.0 item (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Chute, Walter, "The Balanced Aquarium and It's Inhabitants", 1930; 1.0 item (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Epstean, Edward, "Memories: Photo-Engraving in New York City, 1889 - 1900", 1943 November; 1.0 item (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Goldeberg, Edna May, "Popular Tropical Fish", 1933; 1.0 item (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - "Good-bye and Hail Walt Whitman", 1892; 1.0 item (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Gordon, Myron, "Functional Anatomy and Evolution of Male Genitalia in Poecilid Fishes", 1935 April; 1.0 item (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Gordon, Myron, "Hereditary Basis of Melanosis in Hybrid Fishes", 1931 July; 1.0 item (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Gudger, E. W., "Pomacentrid Fishes Symbiotic with Giant Sea Anemones in Indo-Pacific Waters", 1947; 1.0 item (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Ives, Frederick E., "Polychrome Photography", 1932 April; 1.0 item (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Jumper, C. H., "Tests of Integral and Surface Waterproofings for Concrete", undated; 1.0 item (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Levy, Louis Edward, "Recollections of Forty Years: A Photo-Engraving Retrospect", 1903 June; 1.0 item (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Masnata, Alicia, "Peces Tropicales: Vida y Costumbres", 1932; 1.0 item (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Myers, George S., "The Amazon and It's Fishes", 1947 March; 7.0 items (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Myers, George S., "Salt Tolerance of Fresh-Water Fish Groups in Relation to Zoogeographical Problems", 1949; 1.0 item (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Myers, George S., "Usage of Anadromous, Catadromous and Allied Terms for Migratory Fishes", 1949 June 30; 1.0 item (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - New York Zoological Society, "Report of the Director of the Aquarium", 1935 June; 1.0 item (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Pennel, Francis W., "Reconsideration of the Bacopa-Herpestis Problem of the Scrophulariaceae", 1946 June 19; 1.0 item (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Roberts, Mervine, "Beginning the Aquarium", 1956; 1.0 item (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Schultz, Leonard, "The Catfishes of Venezuela", 1944; 1.0 item (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Short Biography of William T. Innes, undated; 1.0 item (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Sorge, Hermann, "Anatomische Untersuchungen Am Bitterling", undated; 1.0 item (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Wendt, Albert, "Die Aquarienpflanzen In Wort Und Bild", undated; 2.0 items (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Walterstorff, W., "Blatter Fur Aquarien: U-Terrarienkunde", 1933 June 15; 1.0 item (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Series V. Printed Materials
  - Akavariet: Organ for sveriges Akvarieforeningar, 1935; 4.0 items (Box 9, Folder 1)